<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ListaSG</string>
    <string name="maomao">Kusuriya no Hitorigoto</string>
    <string name="maomao_description">Maomao must help keep Consort Gyokuyou safe during her pregnancy. An imperial consort being with child is supposed to be a matter of the utmost secrecy, but this is the rear palace, where maneuvering and backstabbing are as commonplace as banter and tea parties. Threats seem to lurk around every corner—but it\'s not just the rear palace keeping busy. Jinshi finds himself struggling to entertain a most unusual request from a pair of visiting ambassadors. Later, he\'s invited to an important gathering in a faraway place—but who knows what dangers might be waiting for him?</string>
    <string name="berserk">Berserk</string>
    <string name="berserk_drescription">A mysterious warrior calling himself The Black Swordsman is out to get the King of a country called Midland. As he battles the king\'s henchmen, their cries of pain and the spilling blood take this relentless warrior\'s mind back in time to the path that led him to his current state.

On just any day, a pack of hooligans are harassing a young lady in distress when all of a sudden, they\'re under attack. The Black Swordsman has returned. He wields a giant sword as large as his grudge against the king. When alone in the woods, the Black Swordsman has a flash back to years past and his trials and tribulations in the Band of the Hawk, a successful band of mercenaries under the charismatic leadership of Griffith, a man driven by the ambition to become king.</string>
    <string name="ghost_in_the_shell">Ghost in the Shell</string>
    <string name="ghost_description">"In the year 2029, the world is made borderless by the net; augmented humans live in virtual environments, watched over by law enforcement that is able to download themselves into super-powered, crime busting mecha.\n The ultimate secret agent of the future is not human, has no physical body and can freely travel the information highways of the world, hacking and manipulating whatever and whenever required. "</string>
    <string name="hajime_no_ippo">Hajime no Ippo</string>
    <string name="hajime_no_ippo_drescription">Makunouchi Ippo is an ordinary high school student in Japan. Since he spends most of his time away from school helping his mother run the family business, he doesn\'t get to enjoy his younger years like most teenagers. Always a target for bullying at school (the family fishing business grants him a distinct odor), Ippo\'s life is one of hardship.

One of these after-school bullying sessions turns Ippo\'s life around for the better, as he is saved by a boxer named Takamura. He decides to follow in Takamura\'s footsteps and train to become a boxer, giving his life direction and purpose. Ippo\'s path to perfecting his pugilistic prowess is just beginning ...</string>
    <string name="neon_genesis_evangelion">Neon Genesis Evangelion</string>
    <string name="evangelion_description">Having prevented the Third Impact and thus saving the planet, NERV unexpectedly finds itself under attack. Conscious of Gendou\'s betrayal, SEELE launches a massive attack on Tokyo-3 in order to conclude the Human Instrumentality Project at any cost. NERV must now fight its most fearsome opponent: mankind itself.</string>
    <string name="shingeki_no_kyojin"> Shingeki no Kyojin</string>
    <string name="shingeki_description">Several hundred years ago, humans were nearly exterminated by titans. Titans are typically several stories tall, seem to have no intelligence, devour human beings and, worst of all, seem to do it for the pleasure rather than as a food source. A small percentage of humanity survived by walling themselves in a city protected by extremely high walls, even taller than the biggest of titans.

Flash forward to the present and the city has not seen a titan in over 100 years. Teenage boy Eren and his foster sister Mikasa witness something horrific as the city walls are destroyed by a super titan that appears out of thin air. As the smaller titans flood the city, the two kids watch in horror as their mother is eaten alive. Eren vows that he will murder every single titan and take revenge for all of mankind.</string>
    <string name="bocchi">Bocchi the Rock!</string>
    <string name="bocchi_description">Gotou Hitori is a high school girl who learned to play the guitar because she dreams of being in a band, but she\'s so shy that she hasn\'t made a single friend. However, her dream might come true after she meets Ijichi Nijika, a girl who plays drums and is looking for a new guitarist for her band.</string>
    <string name="yu_gi_oh">Yuu Gi Ou</string>
    <string name="yu_gi_drescription">Mutou Yuugi is a somewhat frail young boy who happens to be a big fan of gaming of any kind. But when he solves an ancient Egyptian puzzle he is granted all the powers of darkness. Now when confronted with danger and injustice, he transforms into a much darker and dangerous form, and proceeds to dish out the justice and punishment for those who so richly deserve it, by defeating them in a game of cards. </string>
    <string name="frieren">Sousou no Frieren</string>
    <string name="frieren_description">Elf mage Frieren and her courageous fellow adventurers have defeated the Demon King and brought peace to the land. With the great struggle over, they all go their separate ways to live a quiet life. But as an elf, Frieren, nearly immortal, will long outlive the rest of her former party. How will she come to terms with the mortality of her friends? How can she find fulfillment in her own life, and can she learn to understand what life means to the humans around her? Frieren begins a new journey to find the answer.</string>
    <string name="devilman">Devilman</string>
    <string name="devilman_description">Fudou Akira, who has become the Devilman, the only being who can fight demons; a being possessing the powers of a demon and a soul of a man. </string>
    <string name="mirai_nikki">Mirai Nikki</string>
    <string name="marai_nikki_description">Yukiteru always rejects offers to go out with friends, preferring to spend the time writing a diary on his cell phone. He has what he believes is an imaginary friend called Deus ex Machina. However, one day Deus asks him to play a survival game along with eleven others. The winner becomes the next Deus ex Machina. In order to win, the contestants must use their diaries of the future to eliminate one another. For Yukiteru to survive, he must team up with another diary holder, a girl named Yuno. </string>
    <string name="sao">Sword Art Online</string>
    <string name="sao_description">In the near future, a Virtual Reality Massive Multiplayer Online Role-Playing Game (VRMMORPG) called Sword Art Online has been released where players control their avatars with their bodies using a piece of technology called Nerve Gear. One day, players discover they cannot log out, as the game creator is holding them captive unless they reach the 100th floor of the game\'s tower and defeat the final boss. However, if they die in the game, they die in real life. Their struggle for survival starts now...</string>
    <string name="ginga">Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu</string>
    <string name="ginga_description">It is late into the 36th century in the ancient Christian calendar; mankind, having developed the technology to travel faster than light speed and colonize many planets, has taken a hold of space, to the point of abandoning Earth almost entirely. Two superpowers comprising almost all the human population have now for one and a half centuries waged to a long stalemate a war for interstellar supremacy: the Galactic Empire and the Free Planets Alliance.

When he was young and poor, Count Reinhard von Lohengramm, a military genius born a noble in name only, saw his sister, Countess Annerose von Grunewald, turned into an Imperial concubine; having once helplessly watched her being practically sold to Kaiser Friedrich IV as merchandise, he now seeks to crush the Emperor and free her. Meanwhile, Yang Wenli, an Alliance commander of similar calibre who really wanted to be a historian and not a soldier, wishes only for some peace and quiet; yet, as he unwillingly grows in relevance, he\'ll see himself duty-bound to protect the Alliance\'s democracy from the threat of the autocratic Empire. The collision of those two masters of tactics and strategy may bring the war to a close, provided, of course, that they aren\'t first backstabbed by their respective countries\' rotten internal politics...</string>
    <string name="hellsing">Hellsing</string>
    <string name="hellsing_description">Vampires exist. It is the duty of Hellsing, an organization backed by the British government, to hide this frightening fact and protect the blissfully unaware populace. Along with its own personal army, Hellsing also has a few secret weapons. Alucard, an incredibly powerful vampire, has been controlled by Hellsing for years. Although he dislikes being a servant to the Hellsing family, he certainly enjoys his job as Hellsing\'s vampire exterminator. Seras Victoria is a fledgling vampire and a former police woman. Although reluctant to embrace her new self, she is still a valuable member of the organization. Integra Hellsing, the current leader, is usually fully capable of fulfilling her duty, but lately, vampire activity has been on the rise. Unfortunately, the cause is more alarming than anything she could have imagined... </string>
    <string name="bunny">Seishun Buta Yarou wa Bunny Girl Senpai no Yume o Minai</string>
    <string name="bunny_description">There is a rumor about a mysterious phenomenon call "puberty syndrome." For example, Azusagawa Sakuta is a high school student who suddenly sees a bunny girl appear in front of him. The girl is actually a girl named Sakurajima Mai, who is Sakuta\'s upperclassman who is also a famous actress who has gone on hiatus from the entertainment industry. For some reason, the people around Mai can no longer see her. Sakuta sets out to solve this mystery, and has he spends time with Mai, he learns her secret feelings. Other heroines who have "puberty syndrome" start to appear in front of Sakuta.</string>
    <string name="fate">Fate/Stay Night</string>
    <string name="fate_description">Shirou Emiya, a high school student and amateur magus twice orphaned by tragedy, is unwittingly dragged into the Fifth Holy Grail War in Fuyuki City, a secret battle royale where seven Masters summon legendary heroic spirits called Servants to fight to the death for an omnipotent wish-granting relic. In this conflict where Servants hide their true identities to protect their weaknesses, Shirou accidentally witnesses a duel and is mortally wounded by the Servant Lancer to preserve the war\'s secrecy, only to be saved by his classmate Rin Tohsaka. When Lancer returns to finish him off, a desperate Shirou accidentally summons the powerful Servant Saber, driving the attacker away and forcing the inexperienced teenager to become a Master in a high-stakes war against powerful rivals.</string>
    <string name="darling">Darling in the Franxx</string>
    <string name="darling_drescription">They dream of one day flying into the endless sky, even though they are painfully aware of how far away the sky is beyond the glass that blocks their flight.

The distant future: Humanity established the mobile fort city, Plantation, upon the ruined wasteland and civilization flourished. Within the city were pilot quarters called Mistilteinn, otherwise known as the "Birdcage." That is where the children live... Not knowing anything of the outside world, and unaware of the vast sky. Their only mission in life was the fight.

Their enemies are the mysterious giant organisms known as Kyoryu. The children operate robots known as FRANXX in order to face these still unseen enemies because they believe that is their purpose in life. Among them was a boy who was once called a child prodigy: Code number 016, Hiro. However, now he\'s a failure and considered unneeded. Those who cannot pilot FRANXX basically do not exist.

One day, a mysterious girl called Zero Two appears in front of Hiro. From her face grew two alluring horns.

"I\'ve found you, my Darling."
</string>
    <string name="citrus">Citrus</string>
    <string name="citrus_description">Fashionable Yuzu imagined the first day at her new school she transferred to after her mother\'s remarriage a bit differently; she didn\'t know it\'d be an ultra-strict and conservative girls\' school. So instead of a sweet high-school romance, she butts heads with the stern student council president Mei - who turns out to be her new stepsister. And she has to learn that hate and attraction are often not that far apart.</string>
    <string name="full_metal">Hagane no Renkinjutsushi</string>
    <string name="full_metal_description">Two brothers lose their mother to an incurable disease. With the power of alchemy, they use taboo knowledge to resurrect her. The process fails, and as a toll for using this type of alchemy, the older brother, Edward Elric, loses his left leg while the younger brother, Alphonse Elric, loses his entire body. To save his brother, Edward sacrifices his right arm and is able to affix his brother\'s soul to a suit of armor. With the help of a family friend, Edward receives metal limbs - automail - to replace his lost ones. With that, Edward vows to search for the Philosopher\'s Stone to return the brothers to their original bodies, even if it means becoming a State Alchemist, one who uses their alchemy for the military.</string>
    <string name="gantz">Gantz</string>
    <string name="gantz_description">" Kurono Kei, a high school freshman, put on airs and thought only about girls. One day, on his way home, he came across a man who accidentally fell from the train platform. He did not care for other people, and at first he enjoyed watching the man who was about to die. However, Katou Masaru, a classmate in his elementary school days, suddenly jumped down from the platform onto the train tracks to help the man there. Being asked for help, Kei reluctantly began to help him. But when they finally got the man onto the platform, saving him, the train arrived at the station. They must have been killed by the train, but instead were instantly transferred into the room of some condominium.  There, they find a black sphere and people who are supposed to be dead like them. And there is no way out of the room. But where is this room? Why are they still alive? And what exactly is that strange sphere in the middle of the room? Kei and Masaru find out, and are horrified by the answers..."</string>
    <string name="vinland">Vinland Saga</string>
    <string name="vinland_description">
As a child, Thorfinn sat at the feet of the great Leif Ericson and thrilled to wild tales of a land far to the west. But his youthful fantasies were shattered by a mercenary raid. Raised by the Vikings who murdered his family, Thorfinn became a terrifying warrior, forever seeking to kill the band\'s leader, Askeladd, and avenge his father. Sustaining Throfinn through his ordeal are his pride in his family and his dreams of a fertile westward land, a land without war or slavery... the land Leif called Vinland.</string>
    <string name="kill">Kill la Kill</string>
    <string name="kill_description">In a high school where students possess uniforms that give them various powers and abilities, student council president Kiryuuin Satsuki rules by force. However, a transfer student named Matoi Ryuuko stands in her way, wielding a scissor sword and a possessed school uniform.</string>
    <string name="bleach">Bleach</string>
    <string name="bleach_description">Kurosaki Ichigo is a teenager gifted with the ability to see spirits. His life is drastically changed by the sudden appearance of a Shinigami (literally, Death god) - one who governs the flow of souls between the human world and the afterlife - named Kuchiki Rukia, who arrives in search of a Hollow, a dangerous lost soul. When Rukia is severely wounded while trying to defeat the Hollow, she attempts to transfer half of her Reiatsu (literally, Spiritual pressure) energy to Ichigo so that he can defeat the Hollow. However, Ichigo takes almost all of her energy, transforming into a Shinigami and allowing him to defeat the Hollow with ease. With her powers diminished, Rukia is left stranded in the human world until she can recover her strength. In the meantime, Ichigo must take over Rukia\'s role as a Shinigami, battling Hollows and guiding souls to the afterlife realm known as the Soul Society.</string>
    <string name="banana">Banana Fish</string>
    <string name="banana_description">
Ash Lynx, a 17-year-old boy, is the boss of a street-kids gang in New York. One day, a man who was murdered before his eyes entrusts him with something. And the last words uttered by that dying man was the phrase, "BANANA FISH". That is the word his brother, Griffin, often mutters. Ash has a destined encounter with Eiji, a kind Japanese boy who comes to New York as a cameraman assistant.
</string>
    <string name="ghoul">Tokyo Ghoul</string>
    <string name="ghoul_description">Tokyo is haunted by mysterious ghouls who are devouring humans. People are gripped by the fear of these ghouls whose identities are masked in mystery. An ordinary college student named Kaneki encounters Rize, a girl who is an avid reader like he is, at the café he frequents. Little does Kaneki realize that his fate will change overnight.</string>
</resources>